That projectile! Clap!
Oh, say clap, inside my body.
Oh, clap!
This is a handmade gun, and if you can knock down the target with a rubber band, you get points.
I see.
Let's do it.
This still looks like fun.
Really?
I like target practice.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
Then I'll be the judge of whether you've fallen or not.
Okay.
I'll give it a shot.
Do I have to take my clothes off?
It's not that easy, is it? Let's take it off.
I'll do it like this.
It's too tight.
Okay, please.
Does this one have a score on it?
This one has a score on it, too.
This one has a score on it, too? This one has a score on it, too.
Here we go.
X selfie
Oh, no!
How many are there?
I don't know.
The staff wants to see the selfies.
That's great!
They did it again.
I don't know why they're posting them again, but I'd like to make it funnier.
Are you ready? Here we go.
What's that?
What is it?
What was that?
Was it?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's on me. I'm sorry.
Sorry, I'll turn it off.
I turned it off.
I knew it. It's gone.
They say it's too funny.
Really?
Wow, thank you.
That's great. You're really sweet to follow up, Anna.
I'm glad.
Here we go... the big one here is Misoka... your followers are so kind.
Here's a big one for you.
I'll be right back.
Smile and hold the gun.
May I? Here you go.
Maybe a cute animal or something.
Maybe something easy to recognize.
I was fishing in a typhoon.
I was fishing in a typhoon, so I'm not really sure...
Oh, no...
Shingtong-oooooooooo! Gwah! It's so hard! But wait, it's cute!
What's wrong with you!
You're a pervert!
Who the hell are you! Who said I should put my legs out!
That's too tight!
I did this for the head nurse.
I guess there's a generation gap, Anna.
Aren't you shallow?
I know!
I don't know, Ana, but if you did, I wouldn't mind taking a picture.
I wish you didn't.
You're cute.
You know what I'm talking about.
Okay, next one.
Next.
It's hard this time of day.
I'm still working on some of these simple ones, like the face. I still have some of these simple ones, like the face.
I think the thin ones will probably score higher.
Have you tried Coke?
It's embarrassing.
This is embarrassing.
Oh, shit! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What the hell is this show?
Is this really going to air?
I don't understand.
What are you doing?
Next!
I'm so embarrassed.
He's so cute!
We should have a photo shoot.
I don't understand.
Here, damn it. I'm going. Did I give you a good tour? I'm going.
Oh, my God, it's gone!
Is it gone?
Yes!
Three?
And a shocking score. 3.
But I'm close to getting paid.
Really?
Yeah.
Because I don't know what score to aim for.
And also because I'm really close.
Really?
Okay, I'll do it now.
This is for real.
Was it just YouTube?
YouTube is tougher than you think.
It stays forever.
It's horrible.
The top one gets a higher score because it's farther away.
It's so thin, it says "can".
Go, go, go!
I've got it! Good! I'm in! That's good!
I think we have a score.
A mimicry!
A mimic!
You're doing a mimic! A mimic! A mimic!
Oh, I just remembered something.
Direct from Akimasa Haraguchi
Ken Shimura.
Oh, I didn't see it.
It only took me a while.
I had to adjust the sound.
It was just a soundcheck.
I'm sorry, Mr. Araguchi.
I forgot everything... how to do it.
Where do you use this?
I was just playing music. I was just playing Monbukagakusho.
I can't stop sweating!
Ano, this is shit!
Okay, not like this, next.
Ano, not like this, next!
There are girls like this, right?
No, there aren't, Ano.
There's no one like her, Ano here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here, no one like her here
I have a friend, but it's hard... but here...
I've got a child here, but it's hard to find a friend.
I don't miss it.
No, it's not a good one.
I can't get it.
When?
When? - When it's the hardest one to hit.
Oh, shit.
I'd like to get paid a little more.
It's like this.
It's been a long time.
I'm sweating a little bit.
Sweat a little bit.
Apples and apples... they're so cute.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sha!
It's not going down!
Strong apple! It didn't fall over.
No, it's a little harder than it looks.
I think it's the kind that easily falls over.
I'd say the smiley face is a good actor.
You're right.
I can't even find a reason anymore.
It's been a little longer since PHS.
Let's move on.
Go, Nico!
He did it! He's down!
I'm going to take a selfie. Let's take a selfie!
He's down!
This is the one once.
Selfie
So many selfies!
Who's the artist?
He wants me to have a bit more of a repertoire.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't do that.
I don't care.
There's a staff member who'd love to see a selfie.
The selfie was too much.
She did change her color.
She changed her color.
It's not that good.
Did you take one of mine?
Take one on Ma-chan's side, too.
I don't care.
What the heck is this?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What the hell is this?
Seriously.
a-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Shall we make that video? Do you want to make that video?
Video
Here we go.
I'm gonna take a look at you. Where is everybody?
You all right? - Yeah. Here's your stethoscope.
Nice and cold.
Oh, shit. I'm not like this.
I'm not like this. I'll go again.
Put it on.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry, it's stuck in my mouth.
Bubba...
I'm no good at this
Oh, my God...
Please give me a break
Please give me a break with the selfies
What the hell is this?
I really don't think Bubu is this high in calories.
I didn't think it would be this high in calories.
It's really high in calories!
I'm surprised.
I'm getting paid a little more for this.
You worked really hard.
You did a great job.
Does that mean you get extra points?
I only got 3, so all of them are better.
Does that mean you get extra points for the Arrow?
Thank you very much.
All the attractions are over here.
It was harder than I thought it would be.
I'm surprised, it was really hard.
So, 166 points in total for the two events.
Yay!
I don't know if I should be happy or not.
I don't know if I should be happy or not, but I think it's expensive.
How much do you get paid? Here's the paycheck.
Double your fee!
Yay! Thank you!
At the end of the day, we had 165 points, clear total.
Wow! I didn't know it was just barely 165.
I didn't know it was close, but it was twice as close.
I'm so happy!
Or, I have a prize worth an estimated one million yen, which would you like?
Two is fine.
It's not good to write well.
I'll take the participation prize, just in case.
I'm happy to do it.
Participation prize.
Here's your participation prize.
It's a prize I made with my own money.
I'm so happy!
A million.
Can you order this for me?
That's great.
This is the estimated million.
Great... now pick two of the characters.
We've all seen this one before.
Seiya and a lot of other people took them home with them.
Everyone took a picture of it.
They hung them in their offices. They even asked me to do the salon.
What should we do with them?
But you said I could use it for fun, right?
We could do a million yen with the kids.
It would be a lot of fun, right?
It's not so exciting now.
But if I play with my kids, is this okay?
I'll give it to you anyway.
It's good luck, right?
I also found a cat camera.
A cat camera? What's that?
It's a pet camera that turns you into a cat.
You're supposed to take a camera like this?
It's a pet camera that takes pictures of you meowing. This is all on the pet camera. Meow.
Does that mean I'm gonna be a cat?
Okay, here's your food.
Here, nip it.
Here's the money.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're done.
Let's go home.
Oh, my God, this is great.
He said he drove with Sosina.
Did you do this?
Sosina did this, too.
You were dressed like this.